Seeno, hello!
We are Maama Senyama, a staffower research student.
I'm Mizuki Yasui.
Yay!
This time, we will be presenting you with these two.
Please do not hesitate to contact us.
Last time, we had Motoi and Mizuki's self-introduction,
So this time, on behalf of the other members, we would like to introduce ourselves.
Okay.
Well, first of all, I would like to introduce the members here.
Yes, I see that you have changed. So you have changed.
Well then!
Her name is Miyu Kurosaka. She is 15 years old and a first-year high school student.
My hobby is dancing. My special skill is drawing illustrations. We have a T-shirt that Miyu drew for us.
Isn't it super cute? From MOA's point of view, Miyu-chan's appeal is that she is an older sister, but she also takes care of the younger members.
She does our hair and makeup, and she makes everyone happy.
I hope you will meet Miyu-chan sometime.
Okay, next. The next member is Ruri Shiraishi. Ruri Shiraishi is a cute first-year high school student.
Her hobbies are camping and baking sweets, and her special skills are dancing and crafts. Her best charm is her outstanding MC ability, and I would like to add that she is a hardworking person.
There were times when she couldn't do something, but she made sure to do it before the next lesson. But by the next lesson, she makes sure that she can do it, and she always brings a level of quality that exceeds expectations three times over,
I respect Mizuki a lot for that. I had never heard of craftsmanship before. But Ruri was into drawing pictures on candy packages for a while.
She used to draw cat faces on the name of the confectionery, or cat faces on the text, and so on.
I want to see it next time. The next one is Riri Takasugi.
Riri is in her third year of junior high school and is 14 years old.
Oh, that's right, it's her birthday. She is 15 years old. Her hobby is watching K-pop, and her special skills are singing and dancing.
From Moa's point of view, Riri's charm is her dancing machine. Riri can easily learn new songs and K-pop songs other than the ones we have done in the lessons,
She is truly a dancing machine when she dances in front of the mirror. One dance after another comes out of her head.
It's amazing. He learns choreography extremely fast. It's so fast that I think he really is a robot or a dancing robot,
He's a great dancer, and he's the dance leader of the staff plastic research students, so he's a dancing machine.
He is a different kind of dancing machine. Next, I would like to introduce Rina Shimada.
She is not in high school either. She is a junior high school student.
Rina's hobby is reading. Her special skills are basketball and snowboarding.
Rinna's charm is her boss baby. Rinna is a boss baby. Among the staff plastic research students.
Boss Baby becomes mute when she gets sleepy or hungry.Boss Baby becomes mute when he is sleepy or hungry.
Normally, he is very talkative. When he gets hungry or something,
Their eyes start to glaze over and their body temperature rises.
The next one is Yu Miyazawa. She is 14 years old and in her third year of junior high school.
Her hobbies are eating and tea ceremony, and her special skills are cheerleading and hair arrangement. What makes Yuu attractive is that she is an adult on the outside, but a child on the inside.
Inside, she is a child. Do you understand? What I want to say is.
She looks like an adult, but she's very serious, but there's something innocent about her. She looks like a child when she runs.
You know what I mean? They're so happy. Even when they're doing muscle training for a lesson, they get everyone's spirits up.
They are always saying, "Let's go! Mizuki helps me out, too.
Okay, let's go to the next one. This is Yu Watanabe.
She is in her first year of junior high school. Her hobbies are cooking and playing games. Her special skills are singing and playing the flute. Yupi's charm is that she is more solid than anyone else.
Yupi knows everything that Moa doesn't know. Ask her one thing, and she'll answer forever.
When I ask him what it is, he tells me this, that, and the other. It's like Mizuki knows everything.
He can play the flute and cook. He is a high-stakes first-year junior high school student.
I want to go there in the future. What is your position?
I don't predict the future. Like a commentator.
So, even though he's the youngest, he's very solid. Everyone's so cool.
Okay, let's move on. The next one is Koharu Sakai.
Koharu is 13 years old and in the second year of junior high school. Her hobbies are playing the piano and singing.
Her special skills are piano, swimming, and running. And her charm is poka-poka.
Koharu is generally poka-poka. Koharu is a little bit "poka poka," right?
And her catchphrase is, "I'll bring you a warm and fuzzy spring. Everything about them, from their singing voice to their gestures and facial expressions, is so warm and fuzzy.
It makes me smile too. They are always squeezing someone, and when they are squeezed, the cancer starts to make them feel warm, and a chain of warmth starts to flow.
When I realized it, all the students were smiling. That's true.
Then, I'll pay a lot of attention to Poha-chan, too. I'm paying a lot of attention to you.
If you pay attention to everyone, you won't be able to see enough.
Okay, let's go next.
Okay, this is Ms. Miyumi Nishimura.
Her hobby is exercising, and her specialty is handball. Miyumi is an energetic boy with a lot of charm.
This is just like the profile.
He is a one-paced boy, but his face looks like a beautiful girl. Yes, he is a beautiful girl, but he is a boy in character.
It's like he challenges everything.
And she's a handball girl, which you wouldn't expect from her looks.
This is it.This is it.
It's stiff. I haven't seen it. Did you watch the video of the match? Mizuki.
You're super good. She's good.
A live high-spawn.
She's really energetic, so I think she brings that energy to the audience.
That's why all the customers are smiling.
So that's how it is!
You're doing a good job. That's great.
Everyone is amazing.
Our next guest is here. This is Aya Shirahama.
She is 15 years old and in her 3rd year of junior high school.
Her hobbies are watching movies, roller-skating, braai-boarding, roller...hmm? No, that's not it.
Braveboarding?
Skateboarding.
I'm good at watching movies, roller skating, braveboarding, and skateboarding.
The attraction I think is friendliness.
She can get along with anyone.
Mizuki, too.
She was brought into the circle of friendliness.
Moa was also taken in.
Please be friendly, too.
Yes, I do.
Okay, next.
Last?
This is Nanoha Aoyama.
My hobbies are singing nursery rhymes and playing the piano.
Her special skill is that she has soft finger joints.
Nanoha's charm is her soothing singing voice.
Yes, I understand. I understand.
I understand.
Her singing voice heals you.
Her charm is her soothing singing voice.
I totally understand.I totally get it.
I'm a healer and my special skill is that I have soft finger joints.
Why do you do that?
Is it a gap moe?
But they are really soft.
It's a feeling that Mizuki can't reproduce.
I'll definitely try to touch them next time.
I guess everyone should pay attention to the song, but also pay attention to the joints of the fingers holding the microphone.
And watch her cute face as she comes down a little bit.
Feel Nana's with your whole body.
Please become captivated by Iroha-chan.
That's right.
Here's an announcement from us.
Please come in!
Yes, on November 23rd, Thursday, a national holiday, at Shirokane-Takanawa 7-Eleven, there will be a live event for the second time for Statler students.
Yay!
This is fun.
I'm so excited.
I'm so happy.
I'll do my best to show everyone that I've been stationed here again.
I'll do my best.
Please come visit us.
I'll be waiting for you.
Okay, how did you like it? Did you get to know the various and exuberant charms of the STAPLA students? Did you get the message?
Yes, I got the message.
Thank you very much. The STAPLER students are appearing at many events this summer,
If you are interested in them, please come and see us.
I look forward to working with you.
My partner so far has been you, Uchihama! Mizuki Yasui.
Bye bye!
This program is
Kakkukun
Natsuki
YoshinukiMr. Yoshiyuki
Mizuki Azu
Eri Eri
Tomohisa
Mr. Kashiten
Ms. Iori
Good night
Mr. Bertie
Toshikazu
This article was sent to you courtesy of
Mizukichi, a stapler research student
With the offerings
I'm going to do something naughty!
Thank you very much.